Sleep.com: Sleep Cycle Tracker

Mattress Firm

GET - On the App Store

View

[](https://www.mattressfirm.com/mattresses/5637147600.c?special_offers=72_Hour_Sale)[72 Hour Sale: Up to 72% off **ends Monday**](https://www.mattressfirm.com/mattresses/5637147600.c?special_offers=72_Hour_Sale) 01:05:19:07[Shop Now](https://www.mattressfirm.com/mattresses/5637147600.c?special_offers=72_Hour_Sale)

Menu

[](https://www.mattressfirm.com/cart "Shopping bag, (0) items")

MattressesBox Springs & Bed BasesSale & ClearancePillowsBeddingFurniture & More

Find a Store

MattressMatcher® Quiz

                                                    Privacy Policy       

Mattress Firm Privacy Policy
============================

_Last updated: March 28, 2024_  
  
Mattress Firm, Inc. and its brands, including Sleep Experts and Sleep.com (collectively, “Mattress Firm,” “we,” “us” and “our”), are committed to making your search for the perfect mattress and a great night’s sleep as pleasurable and easy as possible. Maintaining your privacy is part of that commitment. By interacting with Mattress Firm through our stores, websites, customer service desk, MattressMatcher® application, mobile applications, events, products, and services, you expressly consent to the collection and use of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy. We may change or add to this Privacy Policy, so we encourage you to view it periodically. This Privacy Policy is made available to you for information purposes only and is not a contract between you and Mattress Firm.

What is Not Covered by this Privacy Policy?

If you applied for a Mattress Firm credit card or any other financing or leasing at our stores, events, online, or on your mobile device, this Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you submitted in your application, which was collected by a third-party on behalf of our financing and leasing partners, not Mattress Firm. These partners have their own privacy policies, which we encourage you to review before you submit your application. You may contact our financing and leasing partners directly for information on their privacy policies and for detail on how they use your personal information.  
  
Our stores, websites, applications, events, and services are intended for general audiences only and are not directed at persons outside of the United States or at children less than 16 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from persons outside of the United States or from children under 16 years of age.  
  
If you are an employee or have applied for a job with us, you can review our [Employee Privacy Statement](https://mattressfirm.brightspotcdn.com/fd/03/34d215bc49e59c4406ac9bbf4a03/12.5.2022%20-%20Mattress%20Firm%20Employee%20Candidate%20Privacy%20Policy.pdf). here, which describes information that we collect and use for employment purposes.

Types of Information We Collect About You

During the past year, we have collected the following information about our guests and others. We may collect such information about you:  

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Categories of Information | Information |
| Identifiers | Name  <br>  <br>Signature  <br>  <br>Postal address  <br>  <br>Email address  <br>  <br>Date of birth  <br>  <br>Account login  <br>  <br>Account password  <br>  <br>Telephone number  <br>  <br>Driver’s license number or state identification card number  <br>  <br>Vehicle license plate number  <br>  <br>Bank account number  <br>  <br>Credit/debit card account number  <br>  <br>Comfort and sleep environment preferences  <br>  <br>Special status designation (e.g., first-responder, military, etc.)  <br>  <br>Tax identification number  <br>  <br>Progressive account number and lease identification number |
| Commercial information | Records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies |
| Internet or other electronic network activity | Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing time, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with an internet web site, application, or advertisement |
| Geolocation data | Geolocation data (not more precise than your zip code)  <br>  <br>IP address |
| Inferences | Inferences drawn from any of the above information to create a profile about you reflecting your preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, preferences, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes  <br>  <br>SleepScore® |
| Audio, Electric, Visual, or Similar Information | Recording of customer service calls. In-store video recordings. Transcripts of online chat sessions. |
| Other Attributes | Dwelling type and characteristics (e.g., number of bedrooms)  <br>  <br>Gender  <br>  <br>Net worth  <br>  <br>Income  <br>  <br>Age  <br>  <br>Credit ranges  <br>  <br>Marital status  <br>  <br>Home value  <br>  <br>Home ownership status  <br>  <br>Educational level  <br>  <br>Number of persons in household  <br>  <br>Number of children  <br>  <br>Home price  <br>  <br>Home purchase date |

How Do We Collect Your Information?

We collect information directly from you. We may collect this information when you:  

* Visit our stores, events, or websites
* Register with, or create an account on, our websites or applications
* Respond to a survey given by or on behalf of us
* Buy products or services from us, whether online, in-store or at one of our events
* Contact us by phone, e-mail, online chat, webform or mail
* File a warranty claim or return or exchange a product
* Participate in a sweepstakes or similar promotion sponsored by, or in partnership with, us
* Sign-up to receive emails or text messages from us
* Leave comments or reviews on our websites
* Post a photo or other content or send us a message via our channels on social media platforms like Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter
* If you use any of the MattressMatcher® or DreamHub™ application in any of our stores, events or online
* If you use our Sleep.com mobile app.  You may access the Sleep.com mobile application Privacy Policy [here](https://www.sleep.com/app-privacy-policy).
* If you use our Sleep.com mobile app and show our Sleep Experts any of your sleep tracking results on your mobile app.

We use tracking tools, such as clickstream data, cookies and pixel tags, to collect information from you. You may disable some of these tracking tools by managing your cookie preferences on your internet browser or by enabling the Global Privacy Control signal (which we recognize) through your browser; however, if you choose to use our website, you expressly consent to the use of those tracking tools, including performance and functional cookies, that are necessary for the proper functioning of our websites and cannot be disabled.  

* **Clickstream Data**.  We collect clickstream data, which provides a non-personalized record of your activity on the internet using the items and webpages that you click on.  We use this data to analyze how you use our websites.
* **Cookies**.  We collect cookies, which are small text files that may be stored on your device when you use our websites.  The cookies we use may contain information – such as a unique user ID – or collect information, such as your IP address or if you create an account with us on any of our websites, email address.  Cookies allow us to recognize your device when you return to our website. They also help us to understand how you use our website and to provide you with advertising and content that we think may be of interest to you.
* **Pixel Tags**.  A pixel tag (also known as a web beacon) is a small string of code that represents a clear graphic image.  We use pixels to collect non-personalized information about your activity on our website (e.g., time, date, duration, and number of page views), so that we can improve our website functioning and to provide you with advertising and content that we think may be of interest to you.

We allow third-party companies (e.g., Google and PayPal) to place tags on our digital properties. The tags may collect information about your activity on our websites and may be used by these third parties to provide us with data and marketing analytics, to assist us with creating or effecting advertising campaigns, and to assist with order fulfillment. Our Privacy Policy does not cover these third-party companies. Please contact these third-party companies (e.g., Google and PayPal) directly for more information about their privacy policy and your choices regarding the tags and the information collected by the tags.  
  
We may collect information about you from our advertising networks, financing and leasing partners, data analytics partners and data brokers. We use information collected for marketing purposes, to analyze and enhance data that we have and for other internal business purposes such as performance optimization and resolving chargebacks, disputes and errors related to your finance or lease accounts.  

We may also collect information about you from a friend or family member. A guest may purchase a product and ask that we deliver it to you. A friend may also tag you in one or more of our social media posts to enter into a sweepstakes that we sponsor.

### How Do We Use Your Information?

During the past year, we have used information that we have collected about our guests and others for the following business purposes. We may use the information that we collect about you for the following business purposes:  

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Business Purpose | Information Used |
| **To complete your purchase and create a record of your sales order.** | Name  <br>  <br>Postal Address  <br>  <br>Telephone number  <br>  <br>Email address  <br>  <br>Account login – for online purchases  <br>  <br>Account password – for online purchases  <br>  <br>Record of products or services purchased |
| **To accept and process your payment.** | Name  <br>  <br>Postal address  <br>  <br>Email address  <br>  <br>Telephone number  <br>  <br>Credit/debit card account number  <br>  <br>Financial account number  <br>  <br>Customer number  <br>  <br>Sales order number  <br>  <br>Driver’s license number or state identification card number  <br>  <br>Date of birth |
| **To deliver the products and services that you order or that we provide to you as compensation for your participation in a study that we sponsor and to haul-away your unwanted mattress.** | Name  <br>  <br>Postal address  <br>  <br>Email address  <br>  <br>Telephone number  <br>  <br>Record of products or services purchased |
| **To administer your participation in a sweepstakes, contest or other promotion and report your winnings to a government tax authority.** | Name  <br>  <br>Postal address  <br>  <br>Email address  <br>  <br>IP address  <br>  <br>Special status designation (e.g., first-responder, military, etc.)  <br>  <br>Tax identification number |
| **So that we can market and advertise to you.**  <br>  <br>  <br>We use your information to send you communications about special promotions or offers via regular mail, email and text messaging. We may send you emails if you register on our website or mobile application, Sleep.com, if you create (or allow us to create for you) a DreamHub™ profile, or if you give us your information in one of our stores or pop-up events. We may use information about you collected across different online services and non-affiliated websites and from the various devices you may use, to market to you (including by online ads) based on your interests. For example, if you view a product on our website, you may see ads for that product on our or third-party websites. We also use your information collected from our MattressMatcher® application, Sleep.com mobile application, financing partners and data and analytics partners to make product, service and content recommendations to you.  <br>  <br>We may use your information across all of our brands (e.g., Sleep Experts, Mattress Firm and Sleep.com). | Name  <br>  <br>Postal Address  <br>  <br>Email address  <br>  <br>Telephone number  <br>  <br>Account login  <br>  <br>IP address  <br>  <br>Geolocation data (not more precise than zip code)  <br>  <br>Comfort and sleep environment preferences  <br>  <br>SleepScore®  <br>  <br>Records of products or services purchased, obtained, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies  <br>  <br>Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing time, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with an internet web site, application, or advertisement  <br>  <br>Inferences drawn from any of the information that we collect about you to create a profile about you reflecting your preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, preferences, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes  <br>  <br>Move effective date  <br>  <br>Dwelling type and characteristics (e.g., number of bedrooms)  <br>  <br>Gender  <br>  <br>Net worth  <br>  <br>Income  <br>  <br>Age  <br>  <br>Credit ranges  <br>  <br>Marital status  <br>  <br>Home value  <br>  <br>Home ownership status  <br>  <br>Educational level  <br>  <br>Number of persons in household  <br>  <br>Number of children  <br>  <br>Home price  <br>  <br>Home purchase date |
| **So that third parties and affiliates can market to you.**  <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>We may share your information with third parties who may use the information to market our goods and services or their goods and services to you based on your purchases or interactions with us. | Customer ID number |
| **To provide you with customer service (e.g., warranty claims, exchanges, returns, store locator, answering your questions, etc.).** | Name  <br>  <br>Postal Address  <br>  <br>Email address  <br>  <br>Telephone number  <br>  <br>Account login  <br>  <br>IP address  <br>  <br>Geolocation data (not more precise than zip code)  <br>  <br>Records of products or services purchased, obtained, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies  <br>  <br>Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing time, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with an internet web site, application, or advertisement |
| **To survey you about your experience with us.** | Name  <br>  <br>Postal address  <br>  <br>Telephone number  <br>  <br>Email address |
| **To detect and prevent fraud and criminal activity and to administer our loss prevention program.**  <br>  <br>  <br>We may use your information to protect you and our company, customers, and employees. For example, we collect your signature upon product delivery to establish proof of delivery.  We also track your browsing behavior on our websites, and verify information that you provide at checkout, to detect and prevent fraud.  If you decide to pick up your purchase in-person, we may ask to see your drivers’ license (but will not store a copy of it) to confirm that the person picking up the order is the person that placed the order. If you refuse to show us your license, we may collect your vehicle’s license plate number to establish, as part of our loss prevention program, a record of who picked up the product.  We may also use cameras in our stores to administer our loss prevention program. We may use your information to resolve chargebacks, disputes and errors relating to your finance or lease account. | Name  <br>  <br>Signature  <br>  <br>Postal address  <br>  <br>Driver’s license number or state identification card number  <br>  <br>Credit/debit card account number  <br>  <br>Vehicle license plate number  <br>  <br>Geolocation data (not more precise than zip code)  <br>  <br>Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing time, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with an internet web site, application, or advertisement  <br>  <br>Progressive account number and lease identification number |
| **To conduct internal research and data analytics.**  <br>  <br>  <br>We may use information collected about you to conduct research for purposes of improving our merchandising, sales, marketing, customer experience and real estate strategies and to evaluate our performance.  We may use information collected about your behavior on our websites and applications and your purchase history to make improvements to our websites, applications, stores and our product and service offerings. | IP address  <br>  <br>Geolocation data (not more precise than zip code)  <br>  <br>Records of products or services purchased, obtained, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies  <br>  <br>Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing time, browsing history, search history, and information regarding your interaction with an internet web site, application, or advertisement  <br>  <br>Inferences drawn from any of the information that we collect about you to create a profile about you reflecting your preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, preferences, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes  <br>  <br>Move effective date  <br>  <br>Dwelling type and characteristics (e.g., number of bedrooms)  <br>  <br>Gender  <br>  <br>Net worth  <br>  <br>Income  <br>  <br>Age  <br>  <br>Credit ranges  <br>  <br>Marital status  <br>  <br>Home value  <br>  <br>Home ownership status  <br>  <br>Educational level  <br>  <br>Number of persons in household  <br>  <br>Number of children  <br>  <br>Home price  <br>  <br>Home purchase date |
| **To pay you for goods and services that you provide or to otherwise pay what we owe to you.**  <br>  <br>  <br>If you are a vendor or landlord that is a natural person, we collect your personal information so that we can verify your payment information, report payments that we make to you to the applicable taxing authority (e.g., IRS) and to remit payment to you. If you win a prize under a sweepstakes that we sponsor, we may collect your tax identification number to report your winnings to the applicable taxing authority. | Name  <br>  <br>Postal Address  <br>  <br>Telephone number  <br>  <br>Email address  <br>  <br>Bank account number  <br>  <br>Tax identification number |
| **To communicate with you for business-to-business purposes.** | Name  <br>  <br>Postal Address  <br>  <br>Telephone number  <br>  <br>Email address |

How Long Do We Keep Your Information?

We keep your information as long as we reasonably anticipate needing it to comply with applicable law, to enforce our rights and to support our ongoing business relationship with you, in accordance with our policies. As an example, if you have purchased a product from us, we anticipate that we may need your personal information to:  

* Meet your reasonably anticipated customer service needs (e.g., providing copies of sales receipts and responding to questions that you may have regarding the merchandise and services that you ordered).
* Assist you with any current or future warranty claims.  Please note that the products that we offer often come with warranties that last several years from the date of original purchase.
* Process returns and/or fulfill exchanges.
* Contact you in the event of a product recall or other issue relating to the product or services that you have purchased.

So that we may continue to market and advertise to you, we will not remove you from our marketing list unless you unsubscribe from all marketing communications from us or ask that we delete your information from our records.

How Do We Share Your Information?

We may share information that we collect about you for our business purposes and as legally required or permitted.  
  
**With our Service Providers.**  
  
We may share information that we collect about you with companies that provide us with services in support of our ongoing operations. For example, we allow our fraud prevention vendor, Forter, Inc., to collect information about your activity on our websites, as well as information you may provide at checkout, to detect and prevent fraud. We may also share information about you with payment processors, delivery routers, contractors and schedulers, shippers, product suppliers, product order processors, technical service vendors, companies that conduct surveys on our behalf, and companies, like direct mail providers, that help us market our products and services. These companies must agree to appropriate restrictions on the protection and use of your personal information.  
  
**With our Advertisers and Marketers.**  
  
We may share your information with advertising and marketing partners to provide you with targeted advertising and promotions and to enable you to give us feedback about the products that you purchase from us. For more details, please see the section of this Privacy Policy titled, “Third Party Advertising Partners and Targeted Advertising”.  
  
**With our Financing and Leasing Partners.**  
  
We may share your information with our financing and leasing partners to prescreen you for financing and leasing offers that we may communicate to you. Also, if you purchase a product from us using your Mattress Firm credit card or other financing or leasing applied for in-store, online or at one of our pop-up events, we inform the applicable finance or leasing company of your sales order information. We may also share your information to resolve chargebacks, disputes, errors and fraudulent activity associated with your financing or leasing account.  
  
**With our Suppliers.**  
  
In instances where we do not administer a product’s warranty, we may provide your information to the supplier of the product so that your warranty claim can be handled. We may also share information with our suppliers to respond to your reviews and questions about their products and services. If a supplier is responsible for directly shipping an ordered product to you, we provide your order and contact information to the supplier so that the product can be delivered to you. If you purchase a service contract or extended warranty from us, we provide your sales order and contact information to the provider or administrator of the service contract or warranty so that they can activate your service contract or extended warranty.  

**With Government Authorities.**  
  
We may share your information as required or requested by a governmental agency (e.g., to respond to a court order or subpoena and report payments to applicable taxing authorities).  
  
**With Law Enforcement and Collection Agencies.**  
  
We may disclose your information to law enforcement if we suspect fraud. We may also share your information as part of an investigation or to report actual or suspected criminal activity. We may disclose your information to assist us in collecting a debt owed to us by you.  
  
**With Strategic Business Partners.**  
  
As we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or buy other businesses or entities. In such transactions, your information may be one of the transferred business assets or provided in connection with due diligence for the transaction.  

**At Your Direction.**  
  
We may share your information as requested by you.  

How is Your Information Sold or Shared under the CCPA?

During the past year, we have Sold or Shared the following information that we have collected about our guests and others who reside in California. Please note that in this section of our Privacy Policy, “Sold” and “Shared” have the meanings given to them by the California Consumer Privacy Act.  
  
**Categories of Personal Information Sold or Shared**  

* Internet or other electronic network activity (e.g., collected by cookies and pixel tags)
* Identifiers (e.g., name, postal address, email address, telephone number)
* Commercial Information (e.g., products or services purchased, purchase history)

**Categories of Third Parties to Whom Personal Information was Sold or Shared**  

* Advertising Networks
* Data Analytics Providers
* Data Brokers
* Merchandise Suppliers

### Third Party Advertising Partners and Your Privacy Preferences

We use third-party advertising partners to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These advertising partners may collect information about your visits to our website, and your interactions with our products and services, so that we can provide you with advertising and product recommendations tailored to your interests. The information maybe collected through the use of cookies and pixel tags. In addition to the information about your visits to our website, our advertising partners may also use information about your activities and behavior on other websites and online applications, or from other services and information that we provide them to assist us with “Targeted Advertising”. Targeted Advertising means displaying an advertisement to you where the advertisement is chosen based on information obtained from your activities over time and across non-affiliated websites and online applications for purposes of predicting your preferences or interests. For example, our advertising partners may use information about your visits to websites and online applications that are not affiliated with Mattress Firm to serve you with advertisements for Mattress Firm products and services that align with your interests. Our third party advertising partners may also use the information we provide about you to market their goods or services directly to you. **If you would like to opt-out of Targeted Advertising, as described above, submit your request [online](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/a56eca0a-39e3-4ff6-9f5e-709f23d6ec4e/57e2f861-e620-403d-bc0c-e01bf435b51a), or send a written request to: “Mattress Firm, 3250 Briarpark Drive, Suite 400, Houston, TX 77042, Attn: Legal Department”. If submitting a written request, please include your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address.**  
  
Currently, we use third party-placed tracking pixels and cookies from the following advertising delivery partner(s): Google. In the future we may partner with other companies to provide interest-based advertising, both on and off our websites. If this occurs, Mattress Firm provides you with an opportunity to opt out when these advertisements are served. You may manage your third-party advertising preferences by clicking on the links below:  

* [I would like to opt OUT of Google Analytics Display Advertising](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices for not having this information used by third-party service providers, please visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)  
  
Facebook Custom Audience Ads  
  
We may display interest-based ads to you when you are using Facebook through a tool offered by Facebook called the Custom Audience Tool. This tool allows us to personalize our ads based on your shopping experience with us. The tool lets Mattress Firm convert your e-mail address to a unique number that Facebook uses to match to unique numbers Facebook generates from e-mail addresses of its users.  

* [I would like to opt OUT of Facebook Custom Audience ads](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

Google Custom Match Ads  
  
We may display interest-based ads to you when you are using Google through a tool offered by Google called the Custom Match Program. This tool allows us to personalize our ads based on your shopping experience with us. The tool lets Mattress Firm convert your e-mail address to a unique number that Google uses to match to unique numbers Google generates from e-mail addresses of its users.  

* [I would like to opt OUT of Google Custom Match ads](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

Token-ID Based Targeting  
  
When you use our website, we share information that we collect from you, such as your email address, IP address or information about your browser or operating system, with our identity partners/service providers and and those partners that facilitate the delivery of your information to our advertising partners. These partners return an online identification code that we may store in our first-party cookie for our use in online, in-app, and cross-channel advertising and it may be shared with advertising companies to enable interest-based and targeted advertising.  

E-mail Marketing  
  
If you are opted in to receive marketing e-mails from us and wish to unsubscribe, you can do so by clicking on the Unsubscribe hyperlink at the bottom of the marketing e-mail you receive. You may also choose to opt out of e-mails by sending an e-mail to us at customerservice@mattressfirm.com. If you choose to opt out with this method, please be sure to include the e-mail address that you would like us to unsubscribe.  

Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, the below information applies to you. Certain terms used in this section have the meanings given to them under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”).  
  
**Shine the Light**  
  
Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, if you have an established business relationship with a business, you have the right to request from that business, certain information with respect to the types of personal information that business shares with third parties for those third parties' direct marketing purposes and the identities of the third parties with whom that business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. Submit your request here.  
  
Please note that under California law, businesses are only required to respond to a Shine the Light request once during any calendar year.  
  
**California Consumer Privacy Act**  
  
Pursuant to Sections 1798.110 and 1798.115 of the California Civil Code, you have the right to request that a business disclose to you the following:  
  
(1) The categories of personal information it has collected about you;  
  
(2) The categories of sources from which the personal information is collected;  
  
(3) The business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling or sharing personal information;  
  
(4) The categories of third parties to whom the business discloses personal information;  
  
(5) The specific pieces of personal information it has collected about you;  
  
(6) The categories of personal information that the business sold or shared about you, if any, and the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold or shared, by category or categories of personal information for each category of third party to whom the personal information was sold or shared; and  
  
(7) The categories of personal information that the business disclosed about you for a business purpose, if any, and the categories of persons to whom your personal information was disclosed for a business purpose.  
  
Pursuant to Section 1798.105 of the California Civil Code, you have the right to request that a business delete any personal information about you which the business has collected from you.  
  
Pursuant to Section 1798.106 of the California Code, you have the right to request that a business that maintains inaccurate personal information about you, correct such inaccurate information.  
  
Pursuant to Section 1798.121 of the California Code, you have the right to request that a business that collects sensitive personal information about you to limit its use of your sensitive personal information to that which is necessary to perform the services or provide the goods requested by you.  
  
To exercise any of these rights, you may submit your request [online](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/a56eca0a-39e3-4ff6-9f5e-709f23d6ec4e/57e2f861-e620-403d-bc0c-e01bf435b51a), or send a written request to: “Mattress Firm, 3250 Briarpark Drive, Suite 400, Houston, TX 77042, Attn: Legal Department”. If submitting a written request, please include your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address.  
  
**Do Not Sell or Share My Personal Information**  
  
Mattress Firm does not sell your personally identifiable information in exchange for money. We may, however, share your information with third parties as described in the “How Do We Use Your Information?” and “Third Party Advertising Partners and Targeted Advertising” sections. Pursuant to Section 1798.120 of the California Civil Code, you have the right, at any time, to direct a business that sells or shares your personal information to not do so, even if no money is exchanged. To exercise this right and opt out of the “sale” and “shar\[ing\]” (as such terms are defined under the CCPA) of your information, submit your request [online](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/a56eca0a-39e3-4ff6-9f5e-709f23d6ec4e/57e2f861-e620-403d-bc0c-e01bf435b51a), or send a written request to: “Mattress Firm, Briarpark Drive, Suite 400, Houston, TX 77042, Attn: Legal Department”. If submitting a written request, please include your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address.  
  
No business may discriminate against you on account of your exercise of these rights.  
  
**Metrics**  
  
Below are metrics regarding Access, Delete and Do Not Sell My Personal Information requests submitted pursuant to the CCPA that Mattress Firm received, fulfilled (in whole or in part), and denied between January 1, 2023 and December 31, 2023. These requests include all individuals, not just Californians.  
  
**_Access Requests_**  
  
Number of Requests Received: 495  
  
Number of Requests Fulfilled: 356  
  
Number of Requests Denied: 35  
  
Median Number of Days to Fulfill Requests: 7  
  
**_Delete Requests_**  
  
Number of Requests Received: 120  
  
Number of Requests Fulfilled: 96  
  
Number of Requests Denied: 1  
  
Median Number of Days to Fulfill Requests: 6  
  
**_Do Not Sell Requests_**  
  
Number of Requests Received: 152  
  
Number of Requests Fulfilled: 109  
  
Number of Requests Denied: 10  
  
Median Number of Days to Fulfill Requests: 6  
  
**_Information Request_**  
  
Number of Requests Received: 23  
  
Number of Requests Fulfilled: 5  
  
Number of Requests Denied: 14  
  
Median Number of Days to Fulfill Requests: 6  
  
**_Correct Inaccuracies_**  
  
Number of Requests Received: 14  
  
Number of Requests Fulfilled: 2  
  
Number of Requests Denied: 2  
  
Median Number of Days to Fulfill Requests: 6  
  
**_Opt Out of Targeted Advertising_**  
  
Number of Requests Received: 185  
  
Number of Requests Fulfilled: 139  
  
Number of Requests Denied: 6  
  
Median Number of Days to Fulfill Requests: 6

For Nevada Residents

Mattress Firm does not sell your personally identifiable information in exchange for money. However, if you would like to opt-out of the sale of your personally identifiable information, submit your request [online](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/a56eca0a-39e3-4ff6-9f5e-709f23d6ec4e/57e2f861-e620-403d-bc0c-e01bf435b51a), or send a written request to: “Mattress Firm, 3250 Briarpark Drive, Suite 400, Houston, TX 77042, Attn: Legal Department”. If submitting a written request, please include your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address.

For Washington Consumers

**I. About This Privacy Policy**  
This _Consumer Health Data Privacy Policy_ applies to consumer health data that is collected in the State of Washington with specific rights regarding consumer health data as defined by the Washington My Health My Data Act (the "WMHMDA”). Specifically, it describes the practices of Mattress Firm, Inc. (“Mattress Firm,” “us,” “we,” or “our”) in its capacity as a regulated entity, that link to this Consumer Health Data Policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure, or sale of consumer health data that we collect from Washington consumers (“Washington consumers”, “you”, or “your”). This _Consumer Health Data Privacy Policy_ supplements the _[Mattress Firm Privacy Policy](https://www.mattressfirm.com/privacy-policy)_ and applies solely to Washington consumers as such term is defined under the WMHMDA.  
  
**II. Categories of Consumer Health Data Collected**  
Pursuant to the WMHMDA, Mattress Firm may collect and use your consumer health data, which is defined as personal information that is linked or reasonably linked to a consumer and that identifies the consumer’s past, present, or future physical or mental health status. Specifically, Mattress Firm may collect the following categories of consumer health data from you:  

* Bodily functions, vital signs, symptoms, or measurements of the information described in subsection (8)(b) of the WMHMDA.  

    * Through your use of the Sleep.com mobile application, we collect measurements of your respiration, movement, noise disturbances, and other sleep measurement data (collectively, “Sleep Data”).

    * Via the Sleep.com mobile application, we request permission to read and write health data from the Health app. Thereby allowing the importing of SERVICE sleep parameters into the Heath app. Your Apple® device will only allow Mattress Firm, via the Sleep.com mobile application, to read and write such data if you grant permission via your device’s settings.  
        
    * For users of Google Health Connect, Mattress Firm, via the Sleep.com mobile application, requests permission to read health data from Google Health Connect. Thereby allowing the importing of SERVICE sleep parameters into the Health app. Your Health Connect device will only allow Mattress Firm, via the Sleep.com mobile application, to read such data if you grant permission via your device’s settings.  

* Individual health conditions, treatment, diseases, or diagnosis.  
    * Through your use of the MattressMatcher® web application, we ask to what extent (e.g., often, sometimes, never) your sleep is impacted by sleep disruptors such as pain, allergies, snoring, sleep apnea and acid reflux.  

* Any information that a regulated entity or a small business, or their respective processor, processes to associate or identify a consumer with the data described in Section 19.373.010 (8)(b)(i) through (xii) of the WMHMDA that is derived or extrapolated from non-health information (such as proxy, derivative, inferred, or emergent data by any means, including algorithms or machine learning).  
    * We collect your daily SleepScore®, an assessment of the quality and quantity of your sleep plotted on scale of 0 to 100, that is generated by the Sleep.com mobile application through your use of the Sleep.com mobile application.

**III. Why We Collect and Use Your Consumer Health Data**  
We collect and use this consumer health data to the extent necessary to provide you with the products and services that you have requested from us (such provision, collectively, the “Services”). The Services include delivering to you, as applicable, the Sleep.com mobile application and the MattressMatcher® web application, and providing you with insights and education required to achieve greater understanding of your sleep condition. Such insights may include, but are not limited to, personalized product and service recommendations based on the consumer health data that you provide. Examples of why we collect your consumer health data include:  

* To enable you to track your Sleep Data including sleep duration, sleep onset, sleep staging and other collected information to provide you with a SleepScore® and other key metrics that allow you to take actionable steps to better sleep. Access to your Sleep Data is required for the Sleep.com mobile application to work. 
* To supplement your Sleep Data to improve our ability to provide personalized sleep analysis and recommendations. 
* To provide you with product and service recommendations, including matching you to the recommended mattress via the MattressMatcher® web application.

**IV.** **Categories of Sources from Which Consumer Health Data is Collected**  
We may collect this consumer health data directly from you, as applicable, via the Sleep.com mobile application and the MattressMatcher® web application and when you elect to show any of our Sleep Experts the contents of your Sleep.com mobile application, as well as from the following sources via the Sleep.com mobile application:  

* Google Health Connect, if you have an Android mobile device; or
* iOS Health Application, if you have an Apple mobile device.

**V.** **Your Rights as a Consumer**  
The WMHMDA provides certain rights to Washington consumers with respect to consumer health data, including the rights to access, delete, or withdraw consent relating to such data, subject to certain exceptions:  

* You have the right to confirm whether Mattress Firm is collecting, sharing, or selling your consumer health data and to access such data, including a list of all third parties and affiliates with whom Mattress Firm has shared or sold the consumer health data and an active email address or other online mechanism that you may use to contact these third parties.
* You have the right to access your consumer health data, including a list of all third parties and affiliates with whom Mattress Firm has shared or sold your consumer health data and an active email address or other online mechanism that you may use to contact these third parties.
* You have the right to withdraw consent from Mattress Firm’s collection and sharing of consumer health data concerning you.
* You have the right to request that we delete any of your consumer health data collected from you and retained by us (and direct our affiliates, processors, contractors and third parties to do the same).  

**We cannot discriminate or retaliate against you on account of your exercise of these rights.**  
  
To exercise any of these rights, you may submit your request [online](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/a56eca0a-39e3-4ff6-9f5e-709f23d6ec4e/57e2f861-e620-403d-bc0c-e01bf435b51a), or send a written request to: “Mattress Firm, 3250 Briarpark Drive, Suite 400, Houston, TX 77042, Attn: Legal Department”. If submitting a written request, please include your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address.  

**VI.** **Appeals Process**  
  
If you would like to appeal any decision that we make with respect to any request you have submitted regarding your consumer health data, please submit your request [online](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/a56eca0a-39e3-4ff6-9f5e-709f23d6ec4e/57e2f861-e620-403d-bc0c-e01bf435b51a), or send a written request, noting your appeal, to: “Mattress Firm, Briarpark Drive, Suite 400, Houston, TX 77042, Attn: Legal Department”. If submitting a written request, please include your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address.  

For All of Our Guests **(including Residents of Colorado, Virginia, Connecticut, Utah and Washington)**  

You may request that we:  

* Confirm if we are processing your personal information
* Correct inaccuracies in your personal information
* Delete any personal information about you which we have collected
* Provide you with a portable copy of the personal information we have collected about you
* Opt you out of the sale of your personal information to third parties
* Opt you out of Targeted Advertising (please see the section of this Privacy Policy titled “Third Party Advertising Partners and Targeted Advertising” for detail on how we use Targeted Advertising)
* Opt you of the processing of your personal information in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects on you.

If you would like to exercise any of these choices, submit your request [online](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/a56eca0a-39e3-4ff6-9f5e-709f23d6ec4e/57e2f861-e620-403d-bc0c-e01bf435b51a), or send a written request to: “Mattress Firm, Briarpark Drive, Suite 400, Houston, TX 77042, Attn: Legal Department”. If submitting a written request, please include your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address.

Appeals

If you would like to appeal any decision that we make with respect to any request that you have submitted regarding your personal information, please submit your request [online](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/a56eca0a-39e3-4ff6-9f5e-709f23d6ec4e/57e2f861-e620-403d-bc0c-e01bf435b51a), or send a written request, noting your appeal, to: “Mattress Firm, 3250 Briarpark Drive, Suite 400, Houston, TX 77042, Attn: Legal Department”. If submitting a written request, please include your name, mailing address, telephone number and email address.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time.  
  
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [customerservice@mattressfirm.com](mailto:customerservice@mfrm.com).

Actions
-------

Sign up for our emails & never miss a deal
------------------------------------------

Email Address

Sign up

**Tap into more savings!** Text **MATTRESS** to **[766693](sms:766693?&body=MATTRESS)** to get text alerts for online exclusives & more. Text STOP to cancel. Msg & data rates may apply.

**View our [privacy policy](https://www.mattressfirm.com/privacy-policy.html)**  

About
-----

Help
----

Legal
-----

About

Help

Legal

MattressFirm.com is wholly owned and operated by Mattress Firm, Inc., 3250 Briarpark Dr., Suite 400 Houston, TX 77042 - Copyright 2024 by MattressFirm.com, a Mattress Firm, Inc. Company All rights reserved.

...Show More

††Offer available 7/16/24-10/1/24 at participating Mattress Firm stores only. Taxes and delivery fees must be paid upfront and cannot be charged to your Mattress Firm credit card; upfront payment of taxes and delivery fees will not reduce monthly payment or amount financed. Qualifying purchase is determined prior to taxes and delivery fees. A promo fee, equal to 2% of the amount financed at time of purchase, will be shown as a separate transaction on your billing statement and included in the balance subject to this promo. Any taxes, delivery or other charges included in the amount financed will increase the related promo fee and the required monthly payments. For example, a $950 purchase with $50 in taxes and shipping costs, will be charged a promo fee equal to $20 and $1,020 will be charged to your account. Qualifying purchase amount must be on one receipt. No interest will be charged on the amount financed (including related promo fee) and equal monthly payments are required on such balance until it is paid in full. The payments equal the amount financed (including related promo fee) divided by the number of months in the promo period, rounded up to the next cent. These payments may be higher than the payments that would be required if this purchase was a non-promo purchase. During the last month(s) of the promo period the required monthly payment may be reduced due to the prior months’ rounding. Regular account terms apply to non-promo purchases. For New Accounts: As of 7/16/2024: Purchase APR is 34.99%. Penalty APR is 39.99%. Minimum Interest Charge is $2. Existing cardholders: See your credit card agreement terms. Subject to credit approval. Offer subject to change.   

^TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF OFFER. Offer available 7/16/24-10/1/24 at participating Mattress Firm stores, online via chat or by phone. Subject to credit approval. 3% back on net purchases (purchases minus returns and adjustments) will be paid in the form of a Synchrony Visa Prepaid Card by mail after the following offer requirements are satisfied: (1) you make a qualifying purchase on a Mattress Firm or Synchrony HOME credit card, (2) the qualifying purchase is delivered, and (3) you submit the requested rebate information and documentation. Rebate form must be submitted online or by mail postmarked by 11/1/24. Qualifying purchase amount must be on one receipt. One rebate per qualifying purchase. Cannot be combined with other rebate offers. Maximum rebate of $500 per customer. The Visa Prepaid Card will be sent to your U.S. mailing address within 8 weeks after all the offer requirements are satisfied. If the Visa Prepaid Card is not received after 8 weeks, call 1 (866) 419-4001 or visit mattressfirm.sendmyrewards.com to inquire about status. If the Visa Prepaid Card is not received, you must inquire no later than 1/13/25 or all rights hereunder will expire. This offer is void where prohibited. Synchrony Bank is not responsible for lost, damaged, illegible, postage due or delayed mail. The Visa Prepaid card cannot be used to make payments on the Mattress Firm Credit Card.​

^^TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF OFFER. Offer available 7/16/24-8/12/24 on Purple RestoreTM Cool Touch or RejuvenateTM purchases at participating Mattress Firm stores, online via chat or by phone. Subject to credit approval. 5% back on net purchases (purchases minus returns and adjustments) will be paid in the form of a Synchrony Visa Prepaid Card by mail after the following offer requirements are satisfied: (1) you make a qualifying purchase on a Mattress Firm or Synchrony HOME credit card, (2) the qualifying purchase is delivered, and (3) you submit the requested rebate information and documentation. Rebate form must be submitted online or by mail postmarked by 9/12/24. Qualifying purchase amount must be on one receipt. One rebate per qualifying purchase. Cannot be combined with other rebate offers. Maximum rebate of $500 per customer. The Visa Prepaid Card will be sent to your U.S. mailing address within 8 weeks after all the offer requirements are satisfied. If the Visa Prepaid Card is not received after 8 weeks, call 1 (866) 419-4001 or visit mattressfirm.sendmyrewards.com to inquire about status. If the Visa Prepaid Card is not received, you must inquire no later than 11/24/24 or all rights hereunder will expire. This offer is void where prohibited. Synchrony Bank is not responsible for lost, damaged, illegible, postage due or delayed mail. The Visa Prepaid card cannot be used to make payments on the Mattress Firm Credit Card.

​Synchrony Visa Prepaid Card is issued by Pathward, N.A., Member FDIC, pursuant to a license from Visa U.S.A. Inc. No cash access or recurring payments. Can be used everywhere Visa debit cards are accepted. The funds associated to this Card expire 6 months from the activation date. After the expiration date, you will not be able to use this Card, and any remaining Card funds will revert and be returned to the promotional provider. Card terms and conditions apply. The Mattress Firm credit card is not a Pathward product or service nor does Pathward endorse this offer. Not valid on previous purchases.  See Sleep Expert for details.​ 

**†No Interest If Paid In Full Within 6, 12 or 24 Months on qualifying purchases with your Mattress Firm or Synchrony HOME credit card. Interest will be charged to your account from the purchase date if the promotional balance is not paid in full within 6, 12 or 24 months.** Minimum monthly payments required. Qualifying purchase amount must be on one receipt. No interest will be charged on the promo balance if you pay it off, in full, within the promo period. If you do not, interest will be charged on the promo balance from the purchase date. The required minimum monthly payments may or may not pay off the promo balance before the end of the promo period, depending on purchase amount, promo length and payment allocation. Regular account terms apply to non-promo purchases and, after promo period ends, to the promo balance. For New Accounts: As of 7/16/2024: Purchase APR is 34.99%. Penalty APR is 39.99%. Minimum Interest Charge is $2. A promo fee will be charged equal to 2% of the amount financed on an equal payment no interest promotion of 18 months or more. Existing cardholders: See your credit card agreement terms. Subject to credit approval. Offer subject to change.​  

​\* 0% APR: 3 years with a minimum purchase of $1499 on your Mattress Firm or any Synchrony HOME credit card. 36 monthly payments required. Qualifying purchase amount must be on one receipt. A promo fee, equal to 2% of the amount financed at time of purchase, will be shown as a separate transaction on your billing statement and included in the balance subject to this promo. Any taxes, delivery or other charges included in the amount financed will increase the related promo fee and the required mon...Show More

\*\* 0% APR: 4 years with a minimum purchase of $2499 on your Mattress Firm or any Synchrony HOME credit card. 48 equal monthly payments required. A promo fee, equal to 2% of the amount financed on your Mattress Firm Credit Card at time of purchase, will be shown as a separate transaction on your billing statement and included in the balance subject to this promo. Any taxes, delivery or other charges included in the amount financed will increase the related promo fee and the required monthly paymen...Show More

\*\*\*No interest will be charged on the promo balance if you pay it off, in full, within the promo period. If you do not, interest will be charged on the promo balance from the purchase date. The required minimum monthly payments may or may not pay off the promo balance before the end of the promo period, depending on purchase amount, promo length and payment allocation. Regular account terms apply to non-promo purchases and, after promo period ends, to the promo balance. For New Accounts: As of 7/16/2024: Purchase APR is 34.99%. Penalty APR is 39.99%. Minimum Interest Charge is $2. A promo fee will be charged equal to 2% of the amount financed on an equal payment no interest promotion of 18 months or more. Existing cardholders: See your credit card agreement terms. Subject to credit approval. Offer subject to change. Select promotions may display in online checkout. All promotions are available in store, phone and via chat

Ownership by rental/lease agreement with Progressive Leasing costs more than the retailer’s cash price. Select items only. Cancel or purchase early at any time. Not available in MN, NJ, VT, WI, WY.

Progressive Leasing obtains information from credit bureaus. Not all applicants are approved.
